http://rochester.us.mensa.org/privacy-policy.php

None of us is as smart as all of us. ~ Kenneth H. Blanchard
Rochester Area Mensa    Rochester, New York    Telephone:  585.204.7210
Privacy Policy*
Share this page:
Privacy Policy
Rochester Area Mensa (RAM) respects your privacy.  This document outlines the ways that the Rochester Area Mensa website may collect information from you.
Browsing the Site
Generally speaking, you can visit the pages of the Rochester Area Mensa website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information, but there are portions of the Rochester Area Mensa website that do request personal information.
Member-Only pages
Some sections of this website are reserved for Rochester Area Mensa members only.  To access the members-only pages of the site, you will need to enter your member ID and password.  You may also need to have cookies enabled in your browser.  This information is used to confirm that you are a member in good standing before displaying these limited-access pages.
NOTICE:  The information in the members-only section is for the use of American Mensa members only.  This information must not be shared with nonmembers of American Mensa.  No permission is granted to use any personal information for promotional purposes or for any purposes not directly related to Rochester Area Mensa or American Mensa, Ltd.
Web Forms
Other portions of the site require personal information in order for you to complete certain activities such as contacting Rochester Area Mensa or requesting information.  These pages will ask you to enter personal information such as your name, mailing address, phone numbers, and/or email address.  The information that you type in these forms is necessary to complete the action for which the page is used.
NOTICE:  Information from potential members may be distributed to local chapters to provide information about local member benefits and activities and to arrange testing as necessary.  For our young members, we require parental consent to distribute more information than name, city and state within the organization.
Cookie Policy
The Rochester Area Mensa website uses cookies to provide members-only access to certain portions of the site as well as to complete online transactions.  A cookie is a text file stored on your computer that includes identifying information that can be retrieved later.  To increase security and privacy, American Mensa uses "session" cookies only - that is, the cookies from the American Mensa website work only during your current visit.  Information is not saved for future visits.
Links to Other Sites
The Rochester Area Mensa website includes links to other websites.  Rochester Area Mensa is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites.  You should always read the privacy policy at a website before revealing any personal information.
Policy Changes
We will inform you of any changes to our web policies by posting a notice on our website.  Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice.  The new policy will apply to everyone using our website and will replace any prior policies.
NOTICE:  The RAM Privacy Policy conforms to and resembles that which is set forth by American Mensa, Ltd.  You can view the AML Privacy Policy here.
Click the envelope,
Email your feedback,
Make us happy!
Mensa's purposes are: to identify and foster human intelligence for the benefit of humanity; to encourage research into the nature, characteristics, and uses of intelligence; and to provide a stimulating intellectual and social environment for its members. ~ from the Constitution of Mensa
Rochester Area Mensa
Telephone:  585.204.7210
Our Group
About RAM
Area Maps
Contact Info
Online Contact
To Do
Constitution
As an organization, Mensa has no opinions.  Mensa has no ideological, philosophical, political, or religious views or affiliations.
But as individuals, we tend to make up for it:  Mensans usually have two or more opinions on any given topic.  Bright people have the ability to view almost any issue from several perspectives, often simultaneously.
As an organization, Mensa has no
opinions.  Mensa has no ideological,
philosophical, political, or religious
views or affiliations.
But as individuals, we tend to make up for it:  Mensans
usually have two or more opinions on any given topic.
Bright people have the ability to view almost any issue
from several perspectives, often simultaneously.
Copyright © 2005-2020 | Rochester Area Mensa | All rights reserved | Read More...
Kenneth H. Blanchard is an American author whose extensive career includes over 60 volumes including the co-authored and controversial The One Minute Manager (1982), Whale Done! The Power of Positive Relationships (2002), and Raving Fans: A Revolutionary Approach To Customer Service (1993).
Quote available at:
GoodReads.com
More Info:  KenBlanchard.com
By clicking “Continue” you will be leaving our website and going to:
Rochester Area mensa does not own or operate this external website and is not responsible for any of its content, offerings, or security policies.  Please continue at your own risk.
585.204.7210 - This phone number is available 24/7/365 for voice or text.  We may not always be available to speak with you or respond right away.  If this is the first time you are calling, the automated attendant will ask your name and your response will be recorded for future use.  Be prepared to state your name, and you may include your organization if you like.  Please be aware that this recording process only occurs the first time you call from any particular number.  Don't be afraid to leave a message!
Please remember to tell us the best way to get back in touch with you.
